<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- SPDX-FileCopyrightText: none

     SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kgeotag</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-only OR LicenseRef-KDE-Accepted-GPL</project_license>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <name>KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਕੇ-ਜੀਓ-ਟੈਗ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kgeotag</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KGeoTag</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKGeoTagxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KGeoTag</name>
  <summary>Photo geotagging program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Programa de geoetiquetatge de fotografies</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Programa de geoetiquetatge de fotografies</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Anwendung zum Geotaggen von Fotos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Photo geotagging program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Programa para geoetiquetado de fotos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Valokuvien sijaintitunnisteiden muokkaus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Programme pour photos géolocalisées</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Program geotagging foto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Programma di geotagging delle foto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">სურათებზე გეოტაგების დადების პროგრამა</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">사진 지오태그 프로그램</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Fotoprogramma voor geven van geotags</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Geografisk stadfesting av foto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਜੀਓਟੈਗ ਲਗਾਉਣ ਵਾਲਾ ਪਰੋਗਰਾਮ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Program do geooznaczania zdjęć</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Programa de marcação geográfica de fotografias</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Programa para marcar geograficamente fotos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Приложение для управления геометками в фотографиях</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Program na geotagovanie fotiek</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Program za geokodiranje fotografij</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Program för geografisk lokalisering av foton</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Coğrafi Fotoğraf Etiketleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для роботи з геомітками фотографій</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPhoto geotagging programxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">照片地理标签管理程序</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KGeoTag is a standalone geotagging program. Images can be associated with geographic coordinates by different means: On the one hand, a matching with GPX encoded geodata can be done, on the other hand, the coordinates can be set manually, either via drag and drop onto a map, via bookmarks or by manually supplying them. The coordinates can be stored in the images' Exif header and/or in XMP sidecar files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KGeoTag és un programa de geoetiquetatge independent. Les imatges es poden associar amb coordenades geogràfiques de maneres diferents: d'una banda, es pot fer una coincidència amb les geodades codificades amb GPX, per altra banda, les coordenades es poden establir manualment, ja sigui mitjançant arrossegar i deixar anar sobre un mapa, mitjançant enllaços d'interès o subministrant-los manualment. Les coordenades es poden emmagatzemar a la capçalera Exif de les imatges i/o en fitxers laterals XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KGeoTag és un programa de geoetiquetatge independent. Les imatges es poden associar amb coordenades geogràfiques de maneres diferents: d'una banda, es pot fer una coincidència amb les geodades codificades amb GPX, per altra banda, les coordenades es poden establir manualment, ja siga mitjançant arrossegar i deixar anar sobre un mapa, mitjançant enllaços d'interés o subministrant-los manualment. Les coordenades es poden emmagatzemar en la capçalera Exif de les imatges i/o en fitxers laterals XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KGeoTag is a stand-alone geotagging program. Images can be associated with geographic coordinates by different means: On the one hand, a matching with GPX encoded geodata can be done, on the other hand, the coordinates can be set manually, either via drag and drop onto a map, via bookmarks or by manually supplying them. The coordinates can be stored in the images' EXIF header and/or in XMP sidecar files.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KGeoTag es un programa de geoetiquetado autónomo. Se pueden asociar imágenes con coordenadas geográficas de distintas formas: por un lado, se puede realizar una coincidencia con geodatos codificados en GPX; por otro, se pueden definir las coordenadas de forma manual, ya sea arrastrando y soltando en un mapa, usando marcadores o introduciéndolas a mano. Las coordenadas se pueden guardar en las cabeceras Exif de las imágenes y/o en archivos XMP anexos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KGeoTag on itsenäinen sijaintitietomuokkain. Kuvia voi yhdistää maantieteellisiin koordinaatteihin eri tavoin: toisaalta voi sovittaa GPX-koodattua maantieteellistä tietoa, toisaalta asettaa koordinaatit itse joko vetämällä ja pudottamalla kartalta, kirjanmerkistä tai antamalla ne itse. Koordinaatit voi tallentaa kuvien Exif-otsakkeisiin tai XMP-oheistiedostoihin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KGeoTag est un programme autonome de géolocalisation. Les images peuvent être associées à des coordonnées géographiques de plusieurs façons : d'une part, une correspondance peut être réalisée avec les données géolocalisées encodées dans le format « GPX », d'autre part, les coordonnées peuvent être définies manuellement, soit par un glisser / déposer sur la carte, soit par des signets ou soit en les saisissant manuellement. Les coordonnées peuvent être enregistrées dans l'en-tête « Exif » des images et /ou dans des fichiers associés « XMP ».</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KGeoTag adalah program geotagging mandiri. Citra bisa dikaitkan dengan koordinat geografis dengan cara yang berbeda: Di satu sisi, pencocokan dengan geodata yang dikodekan GPX bisa dilakukan, di sisi lain, koordinat bisa diatur secara manual, baik melalui seret dan lepas ke peta, melalui bookmark atau dengan memasoknya secara manual. Koordinat bisa disimpan di header Exif citra dan/atau di file-file sespan XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KGeoTag è un programma indipendente di geotagging delle foto. Le immagini possono essere associate alle coordinate geografiche in vari modi: è possibile associarle con i dati geografici in formato GPX, oppure possono essere impostate manualmente. Questo può essere fatto sia trascinando l'immagine sulla mappa, sia tramite i segnalibri, o anche fornendone i valori manualmente. Le coordinate possono essere memorizzate nell'intestazione Exif dell'immagine oppure nel file sidecar XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KGeoTag는 단독 실행형 지오태그 프로그램입니다. 사진과 지리 좌표를 연결시키는 데에는 GPX 인코딩된 위치 궤적, 지도에 드래그 앤 드롭, 책갈피, 직접 좌표 지정 등 수동으로도 가능합니다. 지리 좌표는 이미지의 Exif 헤더 또는 XMP 사이드카 파일에 저장됩니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KGeoTag is een alleenstaand programma voor toekennen van geo-tags. Afbeeldingen kunnen geassocieerd worden met geografische coördinaten op verschillende manieren: Aan de ene kant kan een overeenkomst gemaakt worden met GPX gecodeerde geo-gegevens, aan de andere kant kunnen de coördinaten handmatig ingesteld worden, ofwel via slepen en loslaten op een kaart, via bladwijzers of deze handmatig te leveren. De coördinaten kunnen opgeslagen worden in de Exif-header van de afbeelding en/of in XMP-sidecar bestanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KGeoTag jest samodzielnym programem do geooznaczania. Obrazom można przypisać współrzędne geograficzne na różny sposób: z jednej strony, można wykonać dopasowanie z zaszytymi geodanymi zakodowanymi jako GPX, z innej strony współrzędne można ustawić ręcznie, albo poprzez przeciągnięcie na mapę, albo zakładki, albo ręczne wpisanie. Współrzędne te można przechować w nagłówkach obrazów Exif oraz/lub plikach przybocznych XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KGeoTag é um programa de marcação de coordenadas geográficas em fotografias. As imagens poderão ser associadas às coordenadas geográficas de diferentes formas: Por um lado, poderá ser feita a correspondência com os dados codificados em GPX; por outro, poderão ser definidas as coordenadas manualmente, seja por arrastamento para um mapa, através de favoritos ou através da indicação manual das mesmas. As coordenadas poderão ficar gravadas no cabeçalho EXIF das imagens e/ou nos ficheiros acessórios do XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KGeoTag je samostatný program geografického označovania. K obrázkom je možné priradiť geografické súradnice rôznymi spôsobmi: Na jednej strane je možné vykonať porovnávanie s geodátami kódovanými pomocou GPX, na druhej strane je možné súradnice nastaviť manuálne, a to buď presunutím myšou na mapu, pomocou záložiek alebo ich manuálnym zadaním. Súradnice môžu byť uložené v hlavičke obrázkov Exif a/alebo v súboroch sidecar XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KGeoTag je samostojni program za geokodiranje. Slike lahko povežemo z geografskimi koordinatami na različne načine: na eni strani se lahko izvede ujemanje z geokodiranimi podatki GPX, po drugi strani pa koordinate lahko nastavite ročno, bodisi s vlečenjem in spuščanjem na zemljevid, ali prek zaznamkov ali z ročnim vnosom. Koordinate lahko shranite v glavi slike Exif in/ali v priklopnih datotekah XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kgeotag är ett fristående program för geografisk lokalisering. Bilder kan kopplas till geografiska koordinater på olika sätt: Å ena sidan kan en matchning med GPX-kodad geografisk data göras, å andra sidan kan koordinaterna ställas in för hand, antingen med dra och släpp på en karta, via bokmärken eller genom att ange dem manuellt. Koordinaterna kan lagras i bildernas Exif-huvud och/eller i associerade XMP-filer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KGeoTag, bir coğrafya etiketleme programıdır. Görseller coğrafi koordinatlarla değişik yöntemlerle etiketlenebilir: Bir yanda, GPX kodlu coğrafi veri yapılabilir, diğer yanda koordinatlar el ile girilebilir (haritaya sürükle bırak ile, yer imleri ile veya el ile yazarak). Koordinatlar, görselin Exif üstbilgisinde ve/veya XMP yardımcı dosyalarında depolanabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KGeoTag — окрема програма для роботи із геомітками. Ця програма може пов'язувати зображення із географічними координатами у декілька способів: з одного боку, може бути виконано прив'язку до кодованих даних GPX, з іншого боку, координати можна вказати вручну — за допомогою перетягуванні зі скиданням на карту, закладок або вписування координат вручну. програма може зберігати координати у заголовку Exif зображення і/або у додаткових файлах XMP.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKGeoTag is a standalone geotagging program. Images can be associated with geographic coordinates by different means: On the one hand, a matching with GPX encoded geodata can be done, on the other hand, the coordinates can be set manually, either via drag and drop onto a map, via bookmarks or by manually supplying them. The coordinates can be stored in the images' Exif header and/or in XMP sidecar files.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KGeoTag 是一款独立的地理标签管理程序。图像可根据不同的方式与地理坐标相关联：其一是与 GPX 编码的地理位置数据匹配；其二是手动设置坐标，如通过在地图上拖放、通过书签或通过手动输入进行设置。您还可将坐标存储到图像的 EXIF 文件头和/或 XMP 附带文件中。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kgeotag/kgeotag.png</image>
      <caption>Geotagging with KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Etiquetatge geogràfic amb el KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Etiquetatge geogràfic amb KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Geotagging mit KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Geotagging with KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Geoetiquetado con KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Sijaintitiedon muokkaus KGeoTagillä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Géolocalisation avec KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Geotagging dengan KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Geotagging con KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">დაადეთ გეოტაგები KGeoTag-თან ერთად</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KGeoTag로 지오태그</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Met KGeoTag geo-tags toevoegen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Geoznaczenie z KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Marcação geográfica com o KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Marcando geograficamente com o KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Работа с изображениями в KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Geokodiranje z KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Geografisk lokalisering med Kgeotag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">KGeoTag ile coğrafya etiketleme</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Геопозиціювання за допомогою KGeoTag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxGeotagging with KGeoTagxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">使用 KGeoTag 管理地理位置标签</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://kgeotag.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=kgeotag</url>
  <provides>
    <binary>kgeotag</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kgeotag.desktop</launchable>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::irc">#kgeotag</value>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#kgeotag</value>
    <value key="KDE::mailinglist">kgeotag</value>
  </custom>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.3.1" date="2022-09-05"/>
    <release version="1.2.0" date="2021-11-12"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
